Hey everyone, I'm Megan Kelly. Welcome
to the Megan Kelly show. We've got a
former CIA officer coming on in just a
bit who has some wild stories about
being a spy and unique thoughts about
everything from the war in Iran to
Jeffrey Epstein. And I'm really looking
forward to this talk. But we begin today
with Trump's talking about regime change
in Iran uh and the numerous reports that
he's planning big changes to his own
administration. That regime change does
seem underway in some way, shape, or
form. Last night, the New York Times
breaking the story that the president is
considering firing Attorney General Pam
Bondi. Mr. Trump reportedly upset at her
handling of the Epstein files and her
lack of aggression in going after his
political enemies like New York Attorney
General Leticia James and former FBI
Director James Comey at all. The report
was quickly confirmed by multiple news
outlets. According to the Times, Mr.
Trump is considering replacing Bondi
with current EPA administrator Lee
Zeldon and Semaphore. This morning, a
news outlet reporting that uh the
president has informed Miss Bondi that
quote her time as attorney general is
nearing an end. End quote. And a formal
announcement is expected soon. As always
with Donald Trump's Emma for reporting
he could change his mind before going
through with the plan. But that's not
all. The Guardian just as we came to air
dropping a report that Donald Trump is
privately polling his top adviserss
about whether he should replace the
director of national intelligence Tulsi
Gabbard. The answer is no. He shouldn't.
The president apparently upset that
Tulsi did not condemn Joe Kent, the
former National Counterterrorism Center
director who resigned over Joe's
opposition to the war in Iran. Before he
left the government, Kent reported to
Tulsi uh before he resigned. He worked
for her as their chief of staff and then
went over to counterterrorism and did
speak to Tulsi before he resigned. They
spoke to the vice president and then he
went and directly spoke to the president
about leaving. The Guardian also
reporting that Trump is not happy that
Tulsi, a longtime opponent of foreign
interventions, has appeared somewhat
reluctant to defend his actions in Iran.
There's a lot going on here. Uh joining
me now to react to all of this is
Soramari. He's US editor of Unheard and
Shawn Davis who is CEO of The
Federalist.
Don't miss a moment. Subscribe to this
show on YouTube and follow me on Insta,
Facebook, and X. Ever been in a bad
relationship? You know, the kind that
just wears you down. You settle in even
though deep down, you know, this is not
how it's supposed to be. Well, that's
what daily aches and pains can feel
like. You stop expecting to feel good
and you start thinking, I guess this is
just my life now. But it doesn't have to
be. With Relief Factor, you can break up
with pain just like Anthony did. He
wrote, quote, "I was dealing with
debilitating pain and fatigue. I've been
taking Relief Factor for about two
months, and now I'm back to running my
business, fishing, gardening, doing the
things that really matter to me." If you
have back pain, knee issues, or
stiffness slowing you down, Relief
Factor could give you your mobility
back. Relief Factor is 100% drug-free.
It targets the inflammation that causes
pain, helping you move better, feel
better, and actually enjoy life again.
Try the 3-week quick start for just
1995. Go to relief factor.com or call
8004 relief. Break up with pain and get
back to what matters.
Guys, thank you so much for being here.
I can't think of any two guys I'd rather
have on for what we just saw last night
in the news this morning. We got lucky
having you here. Um, so let's start with
the potential firings. Sean, I guess I'm
not shocked he may or may not be
wavering on Tulsi because the Joe Kent
thing clearly was a be in his bonnet,
but I am kind of surprised about the Pam
Bondi thing because my impression of the
Pam Bondi thing was she handled most of
that exactly the way he wanted her to.
So, what do you make of Let's start with
the Bondi report first.
>> Yeah. So, I think to understand the
whole Bondi thing, you have to go back
to the first uh Trump administration.
His initial AG was Jeff Sessions. One of
the first people in Congress who ever
got on his side back in 2015. Trump
thought he would be great. He was an
immigration hawk and he ended up being a
disaster. He turned over the department
to the deep state. He recused himself
during the Russia hoax. Um, and then we
had Rod Rosenstein for several years.
And in comes Bill Bar. So at that point,
Bill Barr was maybe not the most loyal
guy, but was seen as very very
competent. He dispatched the Muller uh
probe and as a special counsel, but then
kind of fell apart at the end. He he
didn't really follow through with what
he needed to do on Russia gate
accountability and then ended up kind of
going crazy towards the end. He and
Trump have a breakup. And I so I think
Trump with Bondi decided that what he
wanted was not someone who may may have
been ideologically on his side. Um, he
wanted someone who was loyal above all
else. He tried the competent but not
loyal thing with bar. This time he
wanted someone who was loyal. I think
unfortunately
uh she was very loyal. Absolutely. She
wasn't particularly competent. I think
she dropped the ball on a ton of things.
The Epstein uh handling was a farce. The
way she handled that initial White House
meeting, the handout of the binders and
and I think it did extreme damage to
Trump the way she handled it. So, I I
don't blame him and I I don't find it
particularly surprising that he's
probably had enough, especially when you
look at what happened with Tish James,
with James Comey, with so many things
falling apart. I think he understands
now, yeah, loyalty is important, but you
need to have somebody who can actually
do the job competently every day.
>> I mean, I'm wondering, Sorb, if he's
seeing his dwindling poll numbers now
and looking for somebody to blame. And
there is no question that when it comes
to Trump's base, the two things that
arguably have hurt him with with that
base, well, we're seeing some erosion
thanks to Iran, but the Epstein files is
definitely on the list. And I don't is
there is there a chance he's blaming Pam
Bondi for that as opposed to himself?
because we watched. Yes, she was way out
ahead of her skis with her PR campaign
around the Epstein client list is on my
desk and all the Fox News appearances
and all that, but like in terms of we're
done giving you any more disclosures,
goodbye that we saw Trump on camera
saying all that himself.
>> Yeah, I think that's the price you pay
when you campaign on dis full disclosure
of the Epstein files and then sort of
reneg on that. Um whether it's for
understandable reasons or not, I think
some of it is understandable. There are
people who are on the so-called list who
I know, you know, just happen to be
there because they had some interaction
with Virginia Jeffrey, but they were not
at all accused of being on the island or
done any wrongdoing. Yet, if that there
was a kind of full uh unredacted
disclosure, their lives would be uh
destroyed. So whatever the reason, the
fact is that I think Pam Bondi is
basically executing what the president
wanted to do some disclosure but not the
full that would be super dis
destructive. So I think the blame lies
there. I will say one thing there is one
specific fra area which is kind of wonky
but it's important and that has to do
with antirust meaning breaking up
monopolistic businesses. That was an
area where kind of leftwing and
right-wing populace had begun to see eye
to eye going back to the first Trump
administration and part of it falls
under the department of justice. There's
a specific antirust unit within the
department of justice and over the past
year you know the person who was put in
charge of that her name is Gail Slater.
She came from JD Vance's office and was
seen as a as a mega populist who someone
who would translate the mega populist
agenda into going after big tech and
other companies. That is not the free
market, right? Businesses colluding to
buy each other and ultimately so that
consumers only have one choice to go to
whether that's in technology or ticket
prices with ticket master and the like.
That's not free market capitalism and
antirust is a way to correct for that.
Unfortunately, the the the Bondi DOJ was
pretty actually bad in that regard. Gail
Slater, the person who was again put in
charge of the antitrust unit was
basically had all her power taken away.
Um firms that had reached basically
settlements with the Department of
Justice were able to sidestep her so
that the normal scrutiny that goes into
how a settlement was reached. has
happened for example with the merger
between two companies Huelet Packard
Enterprise and and and Juniper Networks
that provide like Wi-Fi and networking
services to big stadiums, hospitals and
things like that. They uh ba basically
they reached a settlement with a DOJ but
one that where it was done behind in a
in a in a kind of behind closed doors
literally over cocktails which raises
serious legal questions. And when Gail
Slater's team objected to this, one of
her deputies fi was fired and then
eventually she herself was fired as
well. So it's one of those instances
where um you know what looks like
populism on the campaign trail and then
it under Bondi it cashed out as kind of
crony capitalism. So that was an area of
disappointment. I have no idea whoever
comes next will do anything different.
Gail Slater is now gone and she was seen
as like one of the one of the real
populist anchors of this administration.
I don't think Bondi did right by her.
>> That's interesting. Okay, that's I
didn't know about that. That's that
could be a potential ding she suffered
behind the scenes as opposed to the ones
we saw publicly, Sean, which were, you
know, there in front of the scenes for
all to see. Who could forget this
moment? This is Fox News February 21st
of last year. Sought zero here. DOJ may
be releasing the list of Jeffrey
Epstein's clients. Will that really
happen?
>> It's sitting on my desk right now to
review. Um that's been a directive um by
President Trump. I'm reviewing that. I'm
reviewing JFK files, MLK files. That's
all in the process of being reviewed
because that was done at the directive
of the president from all of these
agencies.
>> So So have you seen anything that you
said, "Oh my gosh,
>> not yet."
Okay, that was an embarrassment. It
turned out, I guess, not to be true or
so they would later tell us. And then
even more recently, Sean, she was asked,
it was at a cabinet meeting and clearly
she was trying to run cover on this
issue and change the subject from
Epstein when she got asked a question to
the Dow, you know, the surging Dow like,
hey, look at this. Uh, it's so much
better. Look what Trump did. And it was
just inept. We we pulled it. We never
got to this a couple months ago, but
here it is.
ZB.
>> The American people need to know this.
They are talking about Epstein today.
This has been around since the Obama
administration. This administration
released over 3 million pages of
documents. Over three million. And
Donald Trump signed that law to release
all of those documents. He is the most
transparent president in the nation's
history. And none of them none of them
ask Merrick Garland over the last four
years one word about Jeffrey Epstein.
How ironic is that? You know why?
Because Donald Trump the Dow the Dow
right now is over the Dow is over
$50,000. I don't know why you're
laughing. You're a great stock trader as
I hear Rasin. The Dow is over 50,000
right now. The S&P at almost 7,000.
And the NASDAQ smashing records.
Americans 401ks and retirement savings
are booming. That's what we should be
talking about.
>> Is it over? Is it over, Sean? Like,
let's be honest. She's not an effective
messenger for the administration.
>> No. And and I think what she didn't
understand and what a lot of people
didn't understand was that the Epstein
case was not just about Jeffrey Epstein.
It was a proxy for a shadow government,
a bunch of corrupt people who could lead
the nation around by the nose, uh get
rich and never have any accountability.
That that's actually what the whole
thing stands for. And I understand that
there's specific crimes that people are
very upset about and want accountability
for. But when Trump kind of went out
during the campaign and and made a big
deal that he was going to be the one to
get all this stuff out, he was going to
be the one who'd get to the bottom of
it, people really believed him and they
said, "Oh, well, finally this is going
to be the guy, this outsider that they
tried to kill, that they tried to put in
prison, that they tried to bankrupt.
This is going to be the guy who's
finally going to hold everyone
accountable." And I think, you know, he
has done that to a large extent, but not
with the Epstein thing. And so you had a
lot of people who really felt
disillusioned when they saw him come out
and say, "Oh, it's a hoax or this and
that." He was very poorly advised by
whoever did that, whether it was the
FBI, whether it was Bondi. And that
began, I think, a series of of
significant missteps from him that
eroded key demographics. When you look
at his victory in 2024,
um, he won every swing state. It was an
overwhelming victory and it was largely
done on the strength of what people were
calling the podcast bros. These are guys
who speak to 20 under 30 men who are
fairly a-political, who are kind of sick
of all the crap, who don't trust anyone,
and they said, "You know what? This
guy's going to be the one who gets it
done." And then you have Bondie get in
there. She does a whole stupid stunt
with Epstein. She ignored everyone who
told her, "Hey, by the way, you should
probably just get a special counsel to
go in and review these items and and and
slowly release them to make sure it's
all done properly." because she wanted
the attention. She wanted to go on
television and talk about it. She wanted
to be the hero. Well, I've got bad news
for you. When you want to be the face,
you're going to be the one who takes the
fall. And it looks like she's finally
taken the fall.
>> That is so right with the influencers.
Who could forget this moment where she
had them all come to the White House.
These are some of the president's most
loyal social media, you know, warriors.
And she humiliated them by having them
to the White House. Um, we were told
that she actually didn't even front to
them when she got them to come that it
was going to be about Epstein. She But
then she handed out these binders and
sent them out understanding that they
would all be photographed by the press
sitting on the White House lawn with the
binders and there was nothing in them.
Nothing new. She humiliated them. But,
you know, it's tough to say. It's B. I
mean, this is just embarrassing to watch
cuz I like these people and I I blame
her. They didn't know that she had effed
them over. Um, so Sorb, it's it's hard
though to blame it squarely on Pam Bondi
when like who could forget this moment.
I said that the other thing was at a
cabinet meeting. It wasn't. It was Pam
Bondi testifying in front of Congress,
but there was this meeting with Trump
and Bondi early on in the Epstein
scandal where we were all It was right
after the the DOJ had released that
two-page memo saying like, "We're done.
You're getting nothing else." This is a
long time ago, right? This is like last
summer. We were all like, "What?" And
then when Trump got on camera, he wasn't
like, "Sorry, never mind." The DOJ went
rogue. This is what happened.
>> So, could you resolve whether or not he
did? And also, could you say why there
was a minute missing from the jail house
tape on the United States?
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Could I just interrupt for a second?
>> Are you still talking about Jeffrey
Epstein? This guy's been talked about
for years. You're asking, "We have
Texas, we have this, we have all of the
things."
And are people still talking about this
guy, this creep?
>> That is unbelievable.
Do you want to waste the time on Do you
feel like answering?
>> I I don't mind answering.
>> I mean, I can't believe you're asking a
question on Epstein at a time like this.
>> Okay. Um, that's not great. All right.
Now, my team is just sending me this.
Um, this is trying to see the source of
this article. Daily Mail. Pam Bondi
begged Trump not to fire her during
dramatic White House showdown as Insider
reveals his final straw. It reports AG.
Pambani begged Trump not to fire her in
an explosive showdown at the White House
after he accused her of an unforgivable
offense. He informed the AG last night
shortly before his Iran speech that she
would soon be leaving the Justice
Department. According to a senior
administration source, she responded by
pleading uh to give her more time in the
role, but Trump remained firm that her
time leading the agency was over. She
was unhappy and tried to change his
mind, said the source. However, the
president told her she was fired and
that an announcement would be made
shortly. The announcement said to be
made on Friday, but is now imminent
because of all the media attention. His
reasoning for the sudden dismissal comes
in part because the president believes
Bondi tipped off Eric Swallwell.
Okay, this is not on our bingo card,
guys. tipped off Eric Swallwell about
the FBI's efforts to release
investigative documents related to his
relationship with an alleged Chinese
spy, our old pal Fangf Fang. The FBI was
preparing a cache of documents on
Swallwell's relationship with Christine
Fang. She's intervening in those
matters. This is a quote. The White
House was not pleased she was
intervening due to her personal
friendship with Swallwell, said the
source. I call on that. I don't
believe that's the reason. I I just
don't believe that I it's over. The the
FBI getting ready to release the file on
Swallwell from 2015, which it reportedly
is, which it reportedly is. They didn't
find any wrongdoing, but Swallwell
doesn't want the report coming out
because he's running for governor and
the the elections May 2nd in California.
I don't believe that. But your thoughts,
S?
>> Yeah, look, there's a sort of great deal
of crumblininology that goes on with any
um Trump administration. I'm trying to
think and I I want to be fair about
this, but it it is remarkable how messy
these Trump administrations are. We're
now a year and a half into the second
one. I'm trying to think back to the
Biden administration and you know, the
guy was really scenile, like drooling
scenile, you know, bless him. But, you
know, they held it together until
fairly, you know, almost to the end
>> because he he wasn't making any
decisions. They were like, "Gee, should
we fire ourselves?" No. Does everyone
agree? Yes.
>> That's exactly right. But, you know,
then then you compare this and look, I
mean, if the if the previous administ if
the first Trump administration is any
guide, if there was indeed a scene that
involved her begging him not to fire
her, you can almost bet that there's
going to be three years of Bondi serving
as a source to the press, getting a book
deal. what I saw up close and of course
like the, you know, the irresponsibility
of this president and so on and so
forth, having, you know, been, you know,
perfectly eager to do those sessions
where they sit around in the cabinet and
each of the cabinet members goes by one
one by one and says, "Sir, your
presidency really is better than Abraham
Lincoln's. It's amazing." And she was
doing that just as much, but she'll be
leaking against him.
>> It's very uncomfortable.
>> It's very uncomfortable. I mean, I'm a
Trump supporter and I like most of the
people in the administration, but the
the cabinet meetings and like the
constant fluffing of Trump is very prov.
It makes me uncomfortable. Like, just
stop. Just like stop with the obligatory
compliment. It reminds me of what I saw
in Russia with Vladimir Putin. If you
watch a press conference over there, I
mean, all the entire Russian press is
like, "Isn't he fabulous? He's even more
fabulous than we thought he was, isn't
he? He's amazing." Now, our press isn't
like that, but certainly the cabinet is.
It's just too much. It's like, okay,
whatever. It's like, it's fine. I
forgive Trump the need to be to have his
ego stroked because he gets just ripped
by everybody so often. So, I get it.
Okay, Sean, here's what I think. I think
it's probably more of what we said in
the intro, which is she's not bringing
indictments against the people who tried
to put him in prison and bring down his
first presidency. You know, we have not
seen an indictment of John Brennan. We
have not seen a renewal of the charges
against Tish James. The Comey matter,
too. uh is on the ropes because of a
judge ruling that the indictment was
improper. And I I bet Trump actually is
very angry about that stuff and maybe is
blaming Pam Bondi. Like if I had to put
my own money on it, that's where I'd put
it.
>> Yeah. I think it's a whole collection of
things. You know, if you look at his
presidency so far, which we forget how
bad Biden was. Thank goodness he he is
president now and we don't have to deal
with all that uh nonsense. But I I think
he's had kind of two major missteps. the
the big political one was the Epstein
thing which we've covered but I also
think his administration had a fairly
significant strategic misstep in how it
was handling what I call the judicial
insurrection these collection of
completely corrupt inferior unelected
district judges to a certain extent
circuit court judges this was something
that started very early in the
administration where you just had a
bunch of judges with no authority to do
this nonetheless saying hey Mr.
President, we get that you're the head
of the executive branch, but you don't
get to do anything unless you get
unanimous consent from a bunch of
chuckleheads with law degrees who manage
to somehow get appointments to district
courts. And I think there was a
strategic uh calculation made early on
that rather than taking them head-on
immediately and saying we're not going
along with your stupid lawless nonsense
here, you can issue all the opinions you
want. We're not going along with them.
We're not going to pretend they're uh
valid and we're going to do what we're
going to do. And if the Supreme Court
wants to step in and somehow back you
up, they can have at it. And I think and
now whether it was at the advice of the
White House Council's office or the AG,
I think Trump now understands that he's
been in a bit of a hole by how his
administration has decided to handle
these courts. And when you add that up
to all the other missteps with Bondi,
the the appearances, uh, the
embarrassing hearings, the Epstein
thing, I I don't see how Trump had any
other decision to make other than it's
time for you to go and we're going to
put someone else in there.
you made some of these comments in a
taped interview we did for our AM update
podcast which we release every day and
my husband and I were listening to it
this morning as we always do over our
coffee and he you really gave him a lot
to think about. He was saying, my
husband was saying like how good your
points were and was saying, you know,
how is it that we have all these
district court judges who have lifetime
appointments who want to, you know, ding
Trump and pretend that they're little
mini presidents and get plaudits at the
Georgetown cocktail parties with no skin
in the game. Like they don't care
anymore if they get chastised by the uh
circuit courts above them who, you know,
depending on the jurisdiction, never
will chastise them anyway. The the only
chance is when it goes up to the Supreme
Court. They don't care. They all hate
Trump so much. They have such TDS. We
never impeach them. We do abide by their
rulings, you know. Anyway, you persuaded
him. And if people missed AM update this
morning, you missed something good. You
can still go back and listen to it on
YouTube or on podcast. Um, here's the
other thing. The Tulsi news, I really
hope now it's the Guardian. So, Reb, I
don't know how great the Guardian
sources are inside the administration.
Um, and what the motive here might be. I
I believe Tulsey Gabbard wants to stay
and that she doesn't think her neck is
on the chopping block, but the report is
um that it is. I'm going to read what
the Guardian has reported. Um Trump has
privately asked cabinet officials in
recent weeks whether he should replace
his DNI, venting frustration that she
shielded a former deputy, meaning Joe
Kent. It's not clear that Trump will
actually fire her over the episode.
There's no standout candidate to take
the job. It's an ominous development for
Gabbard that he's doing this polling
given that he does tend to pull his
advisers when he starts to seriously
consider whether he should change uh a
post. The nature of Joe Kent's departure
and his criticism of the war had already
angered Trump, but he expressed
particular the frustration about
Gabbard, seemingly defending Joe Kent
and appearing reluctant to defend the
administration's position to attack
Iran. He was asked on March 29th, just
days ago, whether he still had
confidence in Tulsi on Air Force One.
Here's what he said in S one.
>> She's got confidence in Tulsi Gavern,
sir.
>> Yeah, sure. Follow up.
>> I mean, she's a little bit different in
her thought process than me, but that
doesn't make somebody not available to
serve.
>> Okay, that was pretty tepid. Yeah, it
doesn't make somebody unavailable to
serve. like that's just not not a
ringing endorsement.
>> Yeah. I think here's what's happened is
what my sources in the administration,
including lots of people who've in the
security apparatus or or the Pentagon,
this is what they tell me is that the
the so-called restraint camp, people who
are conservative but believe that the US
should leave forever wars, especially
wars of regime change and especially in
the Middle East behind. The people who
want to pivot away from that and focus
either on domestic development or
because they see China as the greater
threat. those people of whom Tulsi was
very much one as everyone pointed out
like her 2020 campaign sold uh t-shirts
that said no war with Iran. Those people
won many of the staffing battle inside
the administration meaning they got
these jobs up and down the Pentagon, the
the the intelligence community and so
on. And but what's happened is that
that's not who the people who ultimately
made the really really big policy call
which is to invade
>> Mark Levin did. It's these outside, they
call them outside voices like Mark
Livven, like Senator Lindsey Graham,
like Senator Tom Cotton, these kind of
uber hawks, Miriam Adlesen, who has the
president's ear very close.
>> She's our real president.
>> Well, I wouldn't go so far, but I'll let
you say. So, you say.
>> I'm I'm being facitious, but she's her
$200 million really did get her a bang
for her buck. And so so you know at some
point that that's going to come to a
head is there there are these people in
the administration who were brought on
on the premise that this was going to be
the ad the administration that was not
going to do this one thing which is to
launch a war against Iran a big war
especially rather than like a quick
intervention. So here they are what do
they do and all of them are facing this
pressure. Do they just like grind it out
and grit their teeth and do you know
execute policies that ultimately leave
them unhappy and feel like it's against
their conscience?
>> She's prepared to do that.
>> It may well be or do they resign or even
if they don't want to resign, do they
get um you know thrown out for lack of
sufficient enthusiasm? And I think maybe
she's in that third
>> Right. Right. or lack of sufficient
enthusiasm or in her case there is a tie
to Joe Kent and if the president is
somehow hanging Joe Kent around her yeah
he could potentially make her suffer for
it but Sean I mean we can't I to lose
Joe Kent and then to lose Tulsi Gabbard
too it's like the restrainer wing of the
Republican party which is always which
is already unhappy with Trump is if he
fires Tulsi that's that's not going to
help the poll numbers he doesn't need to
give the neocons another gift. He needs
to worry about the other part of the
Republican party that feels as Tulsi
does, or at least as she did prior to
joining the administration, I'm assuming
she secretly feels the same way, just
keeping a quiet out of loyalty to him,
which is we don't want this war,
right? So, I have something of a
different perspective. Having been a
staffer, I worked on the Hill for a long
time. I worked for a presidential
campaign. And when you're a staffer, you
have I think there's a certain code you
need to adopt, which is that you don't
matter. you are there entirely to serve
the person that you're working for. And
Joe Kent was a staffer. Tulsi is a
staffer. You might even say JD is a
staffer. The only important one there is
Donald Trump. And I think as a staffer
when you have made the decision
internally that I can't work for this
person because I can't in good
conscience uh implement these policies.
I I personally find it distasteful to
see people do the uh big public
spectacle. Here's why I'm quitting. I
think you have a responsibility to
quietly quit and and go your separate
ways. Now, in defense of Joe Kent, he
could have done what so many people in
Washington have done for decades, which
is stew privately and then do everything
he possibly could to backstab and and
delegitimize the person he's working
for. Okay, that that's what everyone in
Washington does. So, bless him for for
actually having old fashioned way.
>> Yeah. Taking a stand and saying, "I
can't do this." But I I have a hard time
faulting Trump for being disappointed
with that because if there's one thing
Trump cannot stand, it's number one
being disloyal and number two making
yourself the story over him. And I love
Tulsi. I think she's great. I think
she's a very important voice to have in
there. But I don't think you can be
surprised when Trump says, "Hey, this
was your guy and he he went and did
that. Are you really on my team?" I I
think that's probably a fair question,
>> right? I think he accurately senses her
skepticism about the war and maybe he
just doesn't want that right now because
he wants all loyalists around him to
promote his agenda.
>> That's how you make really big mistakes
is is the only people who I mean there's
a video going around kind of a downfall
like it's like it's a Hitler movie
making fun of the decision to go to war
and the the Trump in it says like I'm in
this because I I I just brought so many
asers around me and no one to say hey
like Mr. president. Iran is not like
Venezuela. Iran is not like Iraq. It's
going to be a while if we're and it's
going to be a big war. I think you know
like loyalty is very important but
sometimes loyalty means actually putting
your neck out there and saying Mr.
President this is a really bad decision.
>> Yeah. Because Sorb there's no way Trump
isn't seeing the collapse of the co
coalition that put him in office. you
know, the latest polling out. We've
talked on this show this week about the
loss of the Hispanic voters, the loss of
the young voters, the loss of the men.
He's lost men, young men in particular,
but men across the board now no longer
favored Donald Trump. And of course, the
women have hated him for a long time
now. Today, uh, the latest is he's lost
the working class, the workingclass vote
for Trump, which has always been his
bedrock, is now he's underwater with
them. So he sees this and he looks
around for like a clean way to get out
out of Iran. It's not there. It's
because of this escalation trap that
Professor Pap has been talking about
that we're falling into. And then last
night there were reports that he was
going to go out and announce that we
were pulling out. We were deescalating.
We're It wasn't true. I heard nothing
new last night. I heard a restatement of
his truth social posts which basically
say we're staying. He said maybe two to
three weeks, but he said he wants the
Iranians to do what we want them to do
to cut a deal or we're going to do all
the stuff he said in the True Social
Post, which is bomb their uh electric
plants and their energy plants. He
didn't mention the desalination plants,
which he said in the True Social, but
did you hear anything new and what did
you make of last night's White House
address?
Well, I did hear one thing that was new,
which is in a very disturbing way, is
the president um has said, "We, you
know, it's not possible. It's not
possible for the US to pay for Medicaid,
Medicare, daycare." Quote, "We're
fighting wars." And
>> now wait, wait, hold that thought. That
because that wasn't at the White House
address. Correct.
>> But he did, but this is a separate story
and it's you're right. That's where the
working class had a meeting at the White
House. They they put a post up on
YouTube apparently erroneously of his
remarks to this private group and there
was a devastating soundbite by Trump.
It's now been pulled down but everybody
has it. We all have the feed that that
was up there for some time. And here is
the soundbite to which you refer in SAT
>> because the United States can't take
care of daycare.
That has to be up to a state. We can't
take care of daycare. We're a big
country. We have 50 states. We have all
these other people. We're fighting wars.
We can't take care of daycare. You got
to let a state take care of daycare. And
they should pay for it, too. They should
pay. They have to raise their taxes, but
they should pay for it. And we could
lower our taxes a little bit to them to
make up. But we It's not possible for us
to take care of daycare, Medicaid,
Medicare, all these individual things.
They can do it on a state basis. You
can't do it on a federal. We have to
take care of one thing. military
protection.
>> Okay, you go ahead.
>> So th that is a big departure from the
Trump of 2016, from the Trump of 2020
and the Trump of 2024. The whole thing
with Trump was he repeatedly said, "I am
not going to touch your entitlements. I
am not going to touch your
entitlements." including in the 2024 GOP
the Republican platform the one of the
planks is you know protect and preserve
entitlements and ent and that means
social security Medicare medic and
they've even there are even white house
statements you can find in which that
says we are not going to touch Medicaid
either now for the voters who are the
marginal voters whom Trump brought into
his coalition in 2016 then again in 2020
and even bigger in 2024 these are I'm
not talking about the mega hardcore the
mega hardcore. If he converted to Shia
Islam tomorrow, they would continue to
support. But I'm talking about those
marginal voters, half of Hispanic men, a
fifth of African-American men, young men
who are anti-war. For those people, what
stood out about Trump was that unlike
Ted Cruz and Marco Rubio, the kind of
old Republican party of 2015, he would
say, "I'm going to protect your
entitlements and the foreign wars have
been a disaster." This is the complete
reversal from that because he's saying a
Medicaid, Medicare, all of these things
are under the under the chopping under
chopping block potentially and it should
be a state problem. Maybe we give them
some discount which is not how they're
set up. Certainly not for Medicare. And
then but what what is not on the
chopping block is the war I just
launched in Iran which is going to at a
minimum is going to cost 200 billion
which is what what uh is being asked for
from Congress. So that's like literally
a switcheroon. And I'm sorry I know that
was not from the from the the the
original the the address he gave last
night. I didn't hear anything new in the
address last night. No clear timetable,
you know, no sense of even like the
again the shifting of the mission. Is it
to open the straight? Is it to
denuclearize? Is it regime change? All
of these things depending on which Trump
you ask or which member of the cabinet,
it shifts literally every 12 hours. So
whatever. It was another address. It
sounds like we're in for the big war.
>> It shifts along with a message depend no
matter who it's from of we've been
perfectly clear from the start.
>> Yeah.
>> And then
>> what follows is some new like another
explanation that isn't clear. But okay,
whatever. I mean, I really don't care
like I don't I don't I don't care
anymore about like the retroactive
justifications. I just want us to get
out and I don't care what excuse we have
to use. I'm perfectly happy to go along
with the the excuse. I really am. I just
just get out. like his I hope his
adviserss tell him they'll buy it. Yes,
just get out the straight. It's not fair
to the Europeans to say it's your fault.
I mean, it's your problem now. The
straight of Hormone is being closed. You
deal with it. It's not fair, but I don't
care about that either. I just want us
out. I don't want any more troops over
there. And I think he can do it if
enough people get in his ears and if
enough people show him these polls,
Sean, but your thoughts on both the
sound bite we ran um just there and on
the address last night. Yeah. So, I was
actually pretty encouraged by the
address last night and and I am where
you are. Like I I don't think this was a
wise action to take. I think it's a
distraction. I think it's making it
harder to do things that need to be done
here domestically and it was the
domestic agenda that got him reelected.
But, uh, what I saw, I saw a couple
things. So, he he talked about a few
different things. He said the objectives
were largely completed. He said Iran was
no longer really a threat. It's a direct
quote. That regime change wasn't a goal.
that there were maybe two to three weeks
left and that the straight of Hormuz is
just going to have to open up on its
own. So, what I saw in that was an
admission that, hey, we're not going to
do this big ground invasion to open up
the straight. It's not our problem.
Look, we may have been the reason it got
screwed up. You're going to have to deal
with it. I was encouraged by all that
because it suggests to me that he
understands that this is not popular,
that people didn't want it, that it's a
distraction, that it's hurting him. And
it reminded me of a a New York Post
article that ran right after the the war
was launched. And there was a quote in
it that was very uncharacteristically
Trump where he said something along the
lines of, "Well, I don't care what the
polls say. It's the right thing. I need
to do it. I don't care what the polls
say." And it's very, very rare for Trump
to ever say something like that because
it's an implicit admission that what
he's doing isn't popular. I think he's
known all along that this was going to
be a drag, but for whatever reason, he
felt compelled to do it. He felt he had
to do it. The overall vibe and
impression I got from that speech last
night was a president who understood
that it's a drag on him. It needs to be
wrapped up and it's time to move on. And
say what you will about Trump, unlike I
think every other president I have
experienced and seen as an American, the
man does listen. He has a pretty
incredible political radar and political
instinct. It's how he got elected twice,
three times, depending on where you sit.
The guy's not an idiot. He's not a
political neoight. He survived attempts
to imprison and bankrupt and even murder
him, and he's in president again. So, I
I was encouraged because I think I saw a
president who understands this thing's
got to get wrapped up and we got to move
on.
>> I hope you're right. I get a little
worried when I see, you know, Levvin
tweeting out perfect speech, Zorav.
Like, whoa, wait, why is he so happy? I
get nervous. But maybe it's true. Maybe
we're not going to use all those ground
troops that we sent there, the some
5,000. We got 50,000 in the region now,
which is 10,000 more than normal. Um, or
there's always the possibility that the
speech telegraphing a windown over the
next few weeks was a head fake and that
we are going to see the use of those
ground troops. How did you read it?
>> I I I simply don't know. I I think I I
just would not count on this being uh I
I want I want Seawn to be right. I want
this to be basically an indication of
we're gonna like do a bit more and so
it'll look like we've really hurt the
Iranians now and then that gives him
domestic justification to to leave. I
hope that that's correct. But oh, you
know, the pattern has been one of has
been on on a kind of escalatory ladder.
And so what I worry is two kinds of
ground deployments that I either or or
both I think would be terrible. One is
to try to take this Car Island or some
portion of Iran's southern shore. The
problem with that is that that that area
the Iranians have so fortified and I
watch Iranian state TV and you can say
yeah it's all their propaganda and stuff
but at some point there's some nexus
between propaganda and reality and I
think the Iranians really really want
that to happen because it'll get them a
chance to get up close and get some far
more US deaths than they've been able to
achieve. um even if it means they also
rack up lots of deaths, but to them it's
like it's martyrdom, right? They like
glory in it, so they don't mind that.
But if they can rack up like more kills
and it it provides a static target, too.
If you're landing on an island, it's
pretty easy for them to like drone it,
you know, uh uh and other forms of
targeting that they can do. That's one.
The other, which is, I think, even
crazier, is this idea of landing special
forces to try to retrieve several
hundred pounds of enriched uranium
um which are in tunnels. And obviously
the Iranians aren't like cartoon
villains to keep all their enriched
uranium in one underground site. It's
multiple tunnel cities across the
country where they've placed these. So
the idea of sending in special forces on
this to me seems like a wild goose chase
of I laugh because it's but it's grim
because it's also obviously very very
it's a very dangerous thing to do for
those for the special forces uh
operators. So I mean like the only way
to do the really big thing of quote
unquote defeating Iran is to do an
invasion that takes 500,000 troops at a
minimum. And that's what Mark Livin
really wants. It's obvious from all of
living type messaging it'll become a US
problem for two decades
>> short of that like let's not go there.
Let's just leave. I mean I'm just saying
let's please leave. But my problem is I
just can't be sure that in order to like
maintain credibility. He's not tempted
by the escalation trap that eventually
leads to the 500
>> because because why isn't he leaving
now? I mean that I think last night
should have been we're leaving. We did a
lot. here are all the great things we
did and we're piecing out. Like I don't
really know what's happening over two to
three weeks. They said that they hit all
of their targets. They they said they
were running out of military targets
because our our of course our air force
has been so effective. So what are we
hitting? What are we doing over these
three weeks? And and you know is it
going to be escalatory? Guys got to run.
Thank you both so much for coming on
today. Really appreciate it.
>> Thank you. See you both.
Um, okay. Coming up, more reaction to
the Iran speech last night and an
indepth interview with the real live
American spy. I'm going to ask him
everything about the CIA spying on you
and MK Ultra and all the stuff that you
ever wanted to know about the CIA. Don't
go away.
Hey, thanks for watching today's full
episode. If you're new here, throw us a
subscribe. See what you think. Stay in
touch. There's plenty more goodness
where this one came from. As always, we
really do value your feedback. So, email
me, too. Meganme
kelly.com or just leave a comment down
below. I do read them. I meander over
and I scroll through and I find them
very entertaining and really appreciate
the feedback. But in any event, join the
community by becoming a subscriber so
you miss nothing. We value your support.
We may not always agree on positions,
but as you know, I'm very open-minded to
people who disagree with me. That's how
I learn. So thanks and thanks for
trusting us to always talk about it
openly, honestly, and with provocative
conversations. When you are in a
business growth mindset, you know how
much the basic stuff matters, like how
you talk to customers or clients and
keep your team aligned. A more modern
setup makes everything run smoother. So,
I want to tell you about one of our
sponsors, Quo, spelled Quo, the modern
alternative to running your business
communications. Quo works right from an
app on your phone or computer and lets
you keep your existing number, add new
numbers or teammates, and sync your CRM.
Your entire team can handle calls and
texts from one shared number so there's
no mixed messages or missed. Mixed or
missed. And Quo's AI automatically logs
calls, generates summaries, and
highlights next steps so nothing gets
lost. It can even qualify leads or
respond after hours, ensuring your
business stays responsive. Make this the
season where no opportunity and no
customer slips away. Try Quo for free.
Plus, get 20% off your first six months
when you go to quo.com/mk. That's
quo.com/mk.
Quo. No missed calls, no missed
connections.
My next guest is a former CIA officer
who spent more than a decade inside the
agency, eventually rising to become
chief of counterterrorism operations in
Pakistan at the height of the war on
terror after 9/11. And that's some
responsibility. During his time there,
he was involved in highstakes operations
against al-Qaeda, including efforts tied
to the capture of a senior operative.
After leaving the agency in 2004 to work
in the private sector, his life took a
dramatic turn. During an interview with
ABC News in 2007, he became the first US
official to publicly confirm the CIA's
use of waterboarding on terror suspects.
And at the time, I I felt that water
boarding was something that we needed to
do. And as time has passed and has as
September 11th has has, you know, has
moved farther and farther back into
history, um I think I've changed my
mind. And I think that uh waterboarding
is probably something that we shouldn't
be in the business of doing. Why do you
say that now?
>> Because we're Americans and we're better
than that.
>> But at the time, you didn't feel that
way.
>> At the time, I was so angry and I wanted
so much to help disrupt future attacks
on the United States that I felt it was
the only thing we could do.
>> And with Zeda, you think that was
successful?
>> It was.
>> And we have reported that Khaled Shik
Muhammad was also waterboarded.
>> I was out of it by then, but it's my
understanding that he was that he was
also waterboarded. Those were really the
only two
>> to the best of my knowledge. Yes.
>> And bottom line as you sit here now, do
you think that was worth it?
>> Yes.
>> Did it compromise American principles or
did it save American lives or both?
>> It it I think both. It may have
compromised our principles at least in
the short term.
>> That interview put him at the center of
a national firestorm over interrogation
techniques and US policy in the war on
terror. Years later, Kiryaku was charged
under the Espionage Act and ultimately
pleaded guilty with the feds breathing
down his neck to revealing the identity
of two covert CIA officers to
journalists. He believes he was targeted
for speaking out about the enhanced
interrogation program. He ultimately
spent just under two years behind bars.
John says he has no regrets about
speaking out and in recent years he's
become a major player on the podcast
scene, revealing some of the agency's
tactics and strategies and speaking out
about Jeffrey Epstein and what really
motivates US foreign policy decisions.
Former CIA officer and whistleblower
John Kuryaku joins me now. John, what a
pleasure to meet you.
>> Oh, the pleasure is all mine. Thanks for
the invitation.
>> Of course. Uh, I'm really looking
forward to this discussion and I've been
enjoying your podcast tours as well
since you went a lot of places and I'm
like I I got to know this guy. I I
there's so much I want to go over.
Before we get to your amazing story and
background, which is spectacular, um,
can I just get your reaction on where we
are right now in this Iran war because
you know a lot about this and you've
got, I know, strong thoughts on what
we're doing over there. Did you hear
anything last night that that encouraged
you in any way?
>> Not really. What I had been hoping for,
having watched Donald Trump for the last
six plus years, longer than six plus
years, 10 plus years, I was hoping that
he would declare victory and announce
that the boys are coming home. Uh, and
that's not what we saw. What we saw was
that we're winning or we won, which I
don't believe we are. And um, and we're
going to keep fighting for weeks. that's
probably going to stretch into into
months. But one of the things that
really disturbed me the most was the
president threatened again to attack
Iran's uh infrastructure, specifically
its electrical grid. And that is quite
literally a war crime. It's very unusual
for a president to go on TV and
announce, "I'm going to commit a war
crime." But that's what we saw last
night, you know. And I I think that I
think that we we made a policy decision
to
to accept and to believe Israeli
intelligence at face value. I think that
the Israelis had a vested interest in
lying to us and pulling us into this war
to do their dirty work for them. And
that's exactly what happened. The the
Iranians weren't the threat to us.
>> Yep. Uh, I mean it seemed clear because
the administration admitted it early on
and then when they realized that the
public had a strong reaction to that,
started changing that story. Um,
>> I I always get worried when I see Mark
Levin happy or Lindsey Graham happy and
they were very happy last night which
alarmed me. Lindsey Graham was on Sean
Hannity's program. Listen to this five.
>> Do you believe this is this is pretty
much wrapped up in two to three weeks?
In two or three weeks, we'll have
completed the objective of destroying
their ballistic missile program. In
about 2 to 3 weeks, those objectives
will have been met. And how does this
movie end? What people don't realize is
that they were two to three weeks away,
Iran, from going from 60% to 90%
enrichment. Trump said, "Okay, I've got
two or three weeks to act. I'm going to
act now." Two to three weeks that they
had enough material to make eight or 10
nuclear weapons. and Trump blew up their
enrichment facility so they couldn't go
from 60 to 90. But what I learned
tonight, Iran's gonna have a choice in
two to three weeks.
>> By the way, I don't even think they have
two or three weeks, Senator. Uh that's
two or three weeks when their
infrastructure would be blown up.
>> Now, we have two or three weeks left to
achieve our military objectives,
destroying their missile program, making
sure they could never have a pathway to
a nuclear bomb, and putting them out of
the state sponsor of terrorism business.
We're about 2 or 3 weeks away, but at
the end of 2 or 3 weeks, what happens
next?
>> Wow.
>> Do you think he's trying to get a
certain time frame in our heads? John,
>> seems to me like something might happen
in the next two or three weeks.
>> It's just ridiculous. I don't like this
guy is driving our foreign policy. You
know, Megan, I have to say in all the
years that I was in the CIA, literally
every time an Israeli prime minister
came to the United States, and they come
all the time, regardless of who happened
to be the president, whether it was
Ronald Reagan all the way in into Donald
Trump's first term, every single Israeli
prime minister would come and say,
"Please bomb Iran. Please bomb Iran.
Please bomb Iran." And every president
would say, "No, we're not going to bomb
Iran." Until this president. And the
Israelis from 1986,
the Israelis have have been saying that
the Iranians were 6 months away from a
nuclear bomb. Just simply not true. The
the CIA in the last 20 years has written
two national intelligence estimates.
This is a sense of the entire
intelligence community concluding both
times that the Iranians did not have a
nuclear weapons program. Besides the
fact that Ayatah Kamayi, the late
Ayatollah Kamay issued a fatwa, a
religious decree in 2003 saying that it
was a sin to have a nuclear weapons
program and that the government was
forbidden from doing so. There's no
evidence that they had a nuclear weapons
program except for what the Israelis
have been saying, and I think the
Israelis made it up.
>> And our own intelligence assessment, as
we heard from Telsey Gabbard when she
testified publicly, is that they they
did not have a nuclear weapon and that
they were not close to getting a nuclear
weapon. And even our president told us
that their nuclear weapons program was
obliterated last June. So, this is why
many of us are having trouble believing
anything other than Israel had an agenda
and we decided to help them. as you
point out, the same agenda they've had
for many years. There's much, much more
to do. John, stick with us. Got to take
a quick break and we will be back with a
great interview. I I just know it. Next,
let me tell you about Cozy Earth, which
makes relaxing at home so much more
enjoyable. If you have not tried their
robes or slippers yet, you are seriously
missing out, my friends. Their robes are
unbelievably soft, perfect for slow
mornings after a shower or just relaxing
at night. The fabric is breathable,
lightweight, and incredibly comfortable.
It's the kind of robe you put on and
immediately feel more relaxed in. And
their slippers have this plush lining.
They're warm. They're comfortable.
They're easy to wear around the house
all day, which you should. With Mother's
Day coming up, Cozy Earth makes an
amazing gift. Something she will
actually use and appreciate every single
day. And here's the best part. Cozyear
backs everything with a 100 night sleep
trial and a 10-year warranty, so you can
try it completely risk-f free. Go to
cozyearth.com. Use my code Megan for 20%
off. That's cozyear.com, promo code megn
for 20% off. And if you see the
post-purchase survey, mention you heard
about Cozy Earth from this show. You've
been hearing me talk a lot about Pure
Talk lately. Pure Talk is veteranled, so
helping veterans is their north star.
They have donated over half a million
bucks to America's Warrior Partnership,
a fantastic organization that's on the
front lines of preventing veteran
suicide. And Pure Talk's creating
American jobs with a US-only workforce.
Yes, it'd be a lot cheaper to send jobs
overseas like other companies do, but
they're committed to delivering the best
experience possible for their customers.
And Pure Talk service, I mean, they give
you the same towers, the same network,
same 5G coverage as one of the big guys,
but for a fraction of the price. Pure
Talk supports veterans every single day
and creates American jobs. If you want
to give it a shot, dial pound 250 and
say Megan Kelly to switch to Pure Talk.
That's pound 250250
and say Megan Kelly to switch to Pure
Talk, America's wireless company, Pure
Talk.
So, you're at GW University from 82 to
86, a boy from Pennsylvania,
and Middle Eastern studies is your
thing, and one day a professor pulls you
aside and makes an extraordinary
admission and offer to you. Tell us.
>> Right. I I uh got a degree in Middle
Eastern studies at George Washington
University. And to tell you the truth, I
wasn't ready to go into real life yet.
So I stayed for a master's degree in uh
legislative affairs with a focus being
on American foreign policy analysis. And
um I was taking a class called the
psychology of leadership with Dr. Gerald
Post who was an eminent psychiatrist.
He gave us an assignment quite a
controversial assignment to shadow our
bosses and then to write a psychological
profile of our bosses. I did that and
it was a I worked for a I worked for a
sociopath and I called him on it.
And so I got my paper back at the end of
the week and I got an A and Dr. Post
wrote in the margin, please see me after
class. So I went to his office to see
him. He had me close the door and then
he said, look, I'm not really a
professor here. I'm a CIA officer
undercover as a professor here. I'm
looking for people who might fit into
the CIA's culture and I think you would
fit into the CIA's culture. Would you
like to be a CIA officer? And the truth
is, you know, I wanted to go into public
service. I wanted to see the world. But
the real truth was I was getting married
in six weeks and I didn't have a job. So
I said, "Yeah, sure. I'd love to join
the CIA." And the next thing I knew, I
was in the CIA.
So what was it about you just your
ability to profile people?
>> That was the start of it. Yes. It turned
out that I was hired by the office that
he had created about 6 years earlier
called the political psychology
division. So I was assigned to Iraq. I
became Saddam Hussein's classified
biographer. Um and I did that for years
before um making what at the time was
very unusual switch to uh
counterterrorism operations. But uh the
agency gave me opportunity after
opportunity. I learned to speak fluent
Arabic that went with the fluent Greek
that I had. And um yeah, I mean one day
you're sitting in a college class and
the next day you're in the Oval Office
trying to think of, you know, how not to
sound like an idiot when you're speaking
to the president. And uh yeah, the rest
uh the rest was history.
And so do you do you are you was this a
kind of hire that you could tell anybody
about like when you join the CIA or did
they say no your cover is going to be
you too are a university professor?
>> Well at the beginning I was an overt
employee so I wasn't under formal cover
but what that meant for all intents and
purposes was that I could tell those
closest to me that I was working for the
CIA and then that was it. I mean even my
own wife she knew that I was a CIA
officer. She had no idea what I did. Uh,
which caused all kinds of problems later
and frankly it led to our divorce. Uh,
you know, you come home and you say, she
says, "How was your day?" You say,
"Great." What'd you do? Nothing. Who'
you talk to? Nobody. And then your phone
rings at 11:00. And you say, "You know,
the rain in Spain falls mainly in the
plane." And then you leave until 6:00 in
the morning. And that's just not
conducive to a
to a a smooth marriage,
>> a healthy marriage. Did you really use
little phrases like that? Like the pearl
is in the river.
>> Uh sometimes, yeah. Uh sometimes if
you're not close to the person that
you're trying to trigger an emergency
meeting with, it would be easy to say,
"Hey, Constantine, let's have coffee.
I'll meet you tomorrow morning at 9ine."
Well, tomorrow morning at 9 really means
tomorrow morning at 8 in the abandoned,
you know, parking lot behind the sweater
factory because you've arranged that all
in advance. So, if somebody's listening
to your phone, and nowadays everybody's
listening to your phone, they don't have
any idea what you're going to do.
>> Well, I was interested in your I want to
get to all that, but I do I am
interested in your relationship with
your wife. You you've had two wives as I
understand it
>> and I heard you tell the story in part
and I wanted to hear the rest of it.
>> So you were in Greece
>> and I think this is the first wife,
>> right? My first wife
>> and your son your son said something
shocking to you. Can you tell us that
story?
>> Yeah. I was so focused on the job and
and trying not to get killed. You know,
there was a there was a terrorist group
active in Greece at the time called
Revolutionary Organization 17 November.
That was the whole reason why I was in
Greece at the at the in the
at the basis of it all. Uh it was to to
try to infiltrate this group to disrupt
their attacks and really to destroy the
group from the inside. They'd killed the
CIA station chief, two US defense ates,
the Turkish ambassador, the deputy
ambassador, the minister of finance.
They just killed they killed 28 people.
And so
she was uh a first generation American.
Her parents were were from Greece and
she inherited her grandmother's house on
on one of the Greek islands. And so she
started going to the island on the
weekends and taking the kids. I thought
that was a great idea. The kids can get
to know their cousins. Well,
leaving Friday, coming back Sunday
became leaving Thursday, coming back
Sunday, then leaving Thursday, coming
back Monday. The kids are missing
school. And then one day, I'm shaving,
getting ready for for work, and my then
six-year-old is sitting on the floor
next to me, and we're talking about his
day and what his day is going to look
like. And then he said to me, "I told
mommy not to kiss Uncle Stellios on the
lips. I told her to kiss only you on the
lips. and she told me to mind my own
business. I felt like I had been
electrocuted.
And so I went into the bedroom and I
kicked the bed. She said, "What?" I
said, "Who is Stelios?"
And she said, "Where did you hear that
name?" I said, "Who is he?" And she
said, "Don't believe everything a
six-year-old says."
And I I said to her, and I said it very
plainly and clearly at the time, I'm
going to leave right now before I do
something that's going to that's going
to dog me for the rest of my life. And
so I didn't even finish shaving. I
finished shaving at work. I got in the
car and I drove to the embassy. And it
was all downhill from there. As it
turned out, uh 17 November murdered the
British defense atache a few months
later, Steven Saunders. Steven was a
friend of mine. and we were next door
neighbors and um and a couple of months
later they mailed a manifesto to a
leftist newspaper and they said in the
manifesto
we saw the big spy but we knew that he
was armed and he was driving an armored
car so we elected to carry out the
revolutionary sentence on the war
criminal Saunders. Well, I got to the
office and the and the chief said uh he
came just barging into my office. He
said, "Did you see the manifesto?" I
said, "What manifesto?" He said, "The
Saunders manifesto." I said, "They
didn't leave a Saunders manifesto." He
said, "No, they released it today and
you're in it." I said, "What do you mean
I'm in it?" He said, "They set out to
kill you that morning." And I said, "Oh
my god." He said, "You have to go." I
said, "Go where?" He said, "Home." Like
to Washington. I said, "I just dropped
my kids off at school. I can't just up
and go home." He said, "Listen, you get
in an armored car. We're taking you to
the airport. we're going to pick up your
kids. We're going to pick up your wife.
So, we all met up at the airport. And I
said to her, I am so sorry. And she
said, I want a divorce. I'm not living
like this anymore. And so, the plane
landed in New York. I caught a
connection to Washington. She caught a
connection to Cleveland. And that was
the end of it.
>> Was that the end of it for Stillios,
too?
>> Yeah.
Yeah. I uh
>> They didn't wind up together. Oh no,
that guy could barely read. That was uh
No, she was feeling lonely and it was
because I was so focused on the job.
>> Was very hard to maintain a marriage in
the CIA.
>> Very much so. Very very much so. And you
know, I'll tell you another thing. Um
two years later, I I was in Pakistan and
I'm dating a CIA officer and uh in
Pakistan we had this trunk line. So it
was a just a normal phone, but it was a
202 area code. So it's it's like you're
making a local call. So I think we were
like 11 hours ahead of Washington or 10
and a half hours ahead of Washington. So
I would call her uh every morning when I
got to the to the office because it was
already evening the previous day for
her. And one of the guys in my branch um
it they were all retirees in my branch.
They were all either former chief or
deputy chief of Neareastern um
operations.
And um and so one of them heard me say,
"Okay, I love you. Mwah. And I hung up
the phone and he said, "So, are there
wedding bells in the future?" And I
said, "Oh, I don't know. I just got
divorced and I really don't want to be a
two-time loser." And he says, "Two-time
loser." He says, "I've been married four
times." Jim, how many times have you
been married? Jim says, "Five for me."
Bill, how many times have you been
married? He says, "I have four." Dave,
Dave has three. He says, "Two-time
loser." Welcome to the CIA, kid.
>> Wow. I mean, I guess I'm not surprised.
It doesn't really breed intimacy or
honesty. Not to mention your
psychological profiling skills, which if
used against the wrong person could be
an annoyance to a spouse, I'll say,
>> but it's something you're really good
at.
>> And and when you're, you know, you're
going to do a day trip or something or
take your kids to the, you know, Luna
Park or whatever and you're taking some
crazy way, she says, "Where are you
going?" And the answer is, "Well, I
don't want anybody to shoot us on the
way there." And that's like a legitimate
fear.
>> That's a problem.
>> Yeah. Yes. So, tell me about the CIA
because the CIA has a very bad
reputation in the circles that I travel
in. I think most people are very
suspicious of them in today's day and
age. They're not supposed to be spying
on Americans, but they are
>> um they're masters of the dark arts.
They they have people killed.
>> And I think the question is like how
many people like Americans like what
>> what what are the what are the most
shocking things they do in your
experience that you need people to know
about? Americans, that's the $64,000
question right there. Uh the answer is
we don't know because they won't tell
us. You know, years ago when Senator Ran
Paul, the Republican from Kentucky, was
questioning uh then Attorney General
Eric Holder, I think it was in the
Senate uh Armed Services Committee, um
he asked Holder directly, "Does the
president of the United States have the
legal authority to assassinate an
American citizen?" And after some
hemming and hawing, Holder said yes. And
then he asked a follow-up question. Does
the president have the authority to
murder an American citizen on US soil?
And Holder wouldn't answer the question.
Well, we murdered Anoir Alaki, who was a
bad guy, but had never been charged with
a crime. He had never faced his accusers
his accusers in a court of law. He had
never uh stood uh before a jury of his
peers. We just decided we didn't like
his politics. And so we blew him up. And
then a week later, we blew up his
16-year-old son and 16-year-old nephew,
also American citizens. They had never
been accused of a crime. So either we're
going to be a nation of laws or we're
not going to be a nation of laws. We
have to choose. But we can't pretend to
be the one while really being the other.
We need to make a policy decision here.
But may may I answer further your to
answer more specifically your your your
question.
>> Way back in the bad old days in the
early 1970s, a dear friend of mine
started um as a 22-year-old at the
agency and his initial job was in the
counterintelligence center which was
then headed by the notorious James Jesus
Angleton. And on his first day, the
secretary was walking him around the
office and she pointed to an entire wall
of file folders and she said, "You may
find yourself alone in the office every
once in a while. You are not permitted
to look at those files." Well, of
course, what's he going to do? He's 22
years old. As soon as he's alone, he's
going to run and look at the files.
>> And he said, and now he's in his 70s. He
said every single one of those files was
on an American citizen. Now, that was
patently illegal, but they were doing it
anyway. We all thought that with the
Church Committee and Pike Committee um
reforms of 1975 and 1976 that we had
cleaned all that out. And maybe we did,
at least for a while. But September
11th, September 11th changed everything.
and the CIA went back to the bad old
days with largely the support of the
American people at least for a while and
certainly the support of both Democratic
and Republican administrations.
>> So, but what about now? Because what I'm
noticing is I think postcoid we're much
more conspiratorial
>> than we were pre because all of our
conspiracies came trueact during the co
era. So it made it made everybody like I
trust nothing and no one. But you know,
for example, I know there are a lot of
people questioning whether the CIA had
some control over the Butler shooter of
President Trump,
>> right?
>> There's been a question about whether
they had any knowledge whatsoever about
what happened to Charlie Kirk.
>> Um, do you think that the CIA possibly
has any role in in cases like that?
I don't know, but I can tell you it's
absolutely possible. You know, when when
Joe Kent, whether you like Joe Kent's
politics or not, you cannot doubt the
man's patriotism,
he's walked the walk. And if he says
that he was forbidden from having his
analysts follow investigative leads, you
have to ask why.
Why? Why do we not know more about the
Butler shooter and the circumstances
surrounding the Butler shooting? I grew
up 15 miles from Butler. We never missed
a a county fair and farm show. I've been
there a thousand times. Um, that should
have been easy to investigate, right?
They're all patriotic people. It's a red
county and in a red part of the state
and and then the president of the United
States takes a shot to the ear. So why
why were comprehensive full complete
investigations not carried out? Why was
Joe Kent told that he could not pursue
investigative leads in the Charlie Kirk
case? And one other thing about the
Charlie Kirk case that I've always been
confused about, why is the FBI involved
at all? The the crime took place in
Utah. The shooter is from Utah. He set
out that day from Utah. He went to a
location in Utah. This is a state police
case for for this the Utah State Police.
Why in the world is the FBI calling the
shots unless they know something that we
don't know? Unless they know something,
something that they haven't revealed
that indicates,
>> you know, either
cross interstate uh uh some
investigative lead that came across
state lines or some kind of
international involvement. But my god,
transparency is everything. And like you
said, Megan, in the postcoavid area era
where where we've learned definitively
that we can't trust what the government
is telling us, then wouldn't
transparency make that all go away?
>> Well, as I understand it, is I I haven't
really been conspiratorial uh in my
adult life at all, in any part of my
life,
>> but I do I do want to understand the
theories because some of them do turn
out to be right over time. And as I
understand it, the theory kind of
revolves around MK Ultra. Yeah.
>> Like either, you know, they unleash an
operation on a vulnerable target to try
to get that target,
>> possibly the shooter and Butler, to do
what they want him to do. But can you
walk me through Oh, yeah. what you know
about MK Ultra?
>> Sure. MK Ultra was a uh was a CIA
operation that was that was conceived in
1952. It began to be implemented in 1953
and really took hold in 1955. It did a
lot of different things. There were even
sub operations within MK Ultra, MK
Chickwit, MK Midnight something or
other, lots of them. The bottom line was
this.
There was a source that the CIA
recruited, a Chinese communist source
who said that the Chinese government was
experimenting with mind control. That's
where the the idea of the Manurion
candidate came out which led to a
popular movie in the late 19 1950s
starring Frank Sinatra. In fact, the
Chinese were not experimenting on mind
control. The Russians were and the
source was wrong. But the CIA believed
that it was behind the eightball. And if
the Chinese were experimenting in mind
control, then we needed by God to
experiment in mind control and to figure
out if we could sort of create a Chinese
zombie who could then work his way
through the the upper echelons of the
Chinese Communist Party and take over
China and then do away with communism
and we all live happily ever after.
That's how it started. So the CIA went
about doing this in all of the worst
possible ways. Right around the time
that MK Ultra was was being hatched, a
scientist in Switzerland invented
something called LSD.
And LSD did these incredible things. And
it could manipulate your mind. You could
see colors that didn't exist. You could
see people that didn't exist. And maybe
if we micro dosed people with this new
LSD that maybe we could control their
minds. The CIA began by using it on
their own people. Now, we know that one
of those CIA contractors actually jumped
out of a hotel window and committed
suicide because he thought he could fly.
That's been well documented. Then they
decided, you know, maybe experimenting
on our own people uh isn't uh the best
way to go about this. Maybe we should
just experiment on random citizens in
San Francisco.
And so they went to San Francisco, they
rented a safe house. They recruited a
bunch of prostitutes and sent the
prostitutes out on the street to pick up
dates, bring the dates back to the safe
house, dose them with LSD without their
knowledge, and then try to get them to
reveal their innermost secrets just to
see if the CIA could collect those.
Another part of MK Ultra, also in San
Francisco, was they decided to to create
um a virus or a bacterium. In this case,
it was a bacterium that they could just
push out into the air and see how many
people they could infect. They waited
until an unusually foggy day where the
air is very heavy and sitting close to
the ground and all around the city of
San Francisco as well as on the public
transit system they released this
bacterium and eight people came down
with this very rare upper respiratory
infection. So then they tried to couple
that and the release of the bacterium
with the LSD. Can we release LSD into
the air? They experimented in a small
village in France by dosing the yeast in
the village's only bakery with LSD.
Everybody in the in the village ate
bread from that bakery and everybody
went nuts for a day or two. And so that
was another, you know, successful
operation. In the end, um,
nobody's mind was taken over. We didn't
bring down Chinese communism or Russian
communism or anything else. It was a
failure. But then Congress got wind of
it. The Church Committee got wind of it
in 1975 and called the director of
central intelligence to testify and then
at the testimony specifically ordered
him to not destroy the documents. He
immediately went back to CIA
headquarters and told everybody destroy
everything.
That's why what we have today is only
15% of the MK Ultra documents.
Everything else was destroyed in 1975.
Now, he was held in contempt of Congress
and by God, he was fined $150. And um
Right.
>> Yeah. And all the CIA employees chipped
in to pay the $150 fine for him.
>> Yeah. And and a negative presumption was
against him that he had something to
hide. That's exactly right. But I think
as a result of that, it's part of the
reason why people now suspect government
involvement in everything. You know, the
things that we don't feel like we're
getting full transparency on, it's it's
a CIA conspiracy or maybe an NSA
conspiracy or maybe an FBI conspiracy.
>> And it's it's undermining
>> what what probably are CIA and FBI
conspiracies. Do you know what I mean?
like not everything is a conspiracy by
the government, but for sure they are
doing some things that we should know
about. So, how do you tell the
difference?
>> I think you're exactly right. And the
only way to tell the difference
>> is through robust congressional
oversight. Something that we have not
had since the early 1980s. We're screwed
>> because what what are they? They're
cheerleaders for the CIA and the FBI on
the intelligence committees and on the
judiciary committees. They're
cheerleaders. You know, when I got home
from prison, I was invited to uh a
dinner at the Greek ambassador's
residence. And I went there and um there
was a Democratic senator there who
happens to be a member of the
intelligence committee. And I went up to
him. He came up to me actually and he
said, "Hey, welcome home. We were really
pulling for you." And I said, "Uh,
thanks, senator, but I got to tell you,
I I expected more from you. I thought
you would have been more helpful to me."
and he got angry and he said,"Look, it
took everything I had just to not lose
my security clearance." And I said, 'Oh,
you're afraid of them. You're not
overseeing them. You're afraid of them.
And he walked away from me. But I was
right. He was afraid of them. They're
all afraid. And so they just tow the
line. Well, remember who was it that
said uh about Trump like you mess with
the three-letter agency, you mess with
CIA and they will make you pay
>> for the rest of your life. I can't
remember that was Chuck Schumer. He said
they have nine ways from Sunday to make
your life miserable
>> to make you pay. But here's my question
because I heard you on um Diary of a CEO
saying the CIA can they can they can
rest control of your car. You know, our
cars have these big brains now that I
mean, you know, if if the car company
can't like whatever the the service is,
if you get into an accident, you can
just sort of say, "Help me." If they can
get in there, sure, I bet it's hackable
by somebody else to the point where they
could potentially drive your car right
off the road.
>> If they could do that,
>> then why would they ever have to
>> do anything more explicit? Why would
they ever have to do mind control over
anybody at a at a rally in Pennsylvania
if that's what they want? you know, like
there are there would be ways of getting
rid of you that would be so undetectable
and and not suspicious that they could
be doing that all the time. They
wouldn't have to go about mind control,
MK Ultra, LSD. You know what I'm saying?
So, that to me that's that undermines
the theory that they're doing any of
these public executions explicitly or
behind the scenes.
>> I I think that's right. But think of it
this way, too. I'm going to tell you a
little funny little anecdote about one
of my promotion panels. I had been
working with a psychologist in the CIA's
counterterrorism center to come up with
out of outside the box ideas on how to
recruit spies to steal secrets. And she
happened to also sit on my promotion
panel. And she said in my promotion
panel in in great support of my
promotion, she said, "John Kuryaku will
come up with 40 different ideas for an
operation. 36 of them are insane, but
four of them are going to be really
good."
So, imagine sitting around the table and
somebody comes up with an idea to put an
explosive in Fidel Castro's cigar. Well,
that's a stupid idea. If you're going to
get close enough to put an explosive in
the cigar, just shoot him in the head,
for example, if that's what you really
want to do. So there are a lot of people
sitting around a lot of conference room
tables at the CIA coming up with really
stupid ideas and then there are nodding
heads all the all around the table
saying, "Yeah, that's a great idea. We
should do that." So, you know, the
bottom line is this. We know thanks to
Wikileaks and the Vault 7 revelations
that the CIA can remotely take over your
car. They can make you drive off a
bridge or into a tree or into an
abutment and and kill you if they want
to. They can turn your smart TV into a
microphone. They can reverse engineer
your speaker to turn into a microphone
so they can listen to everything you're
saying even when the TV is off. The the
technology is 20 years ahead of what
anybody else thinks the technology is.
>> I mean, I don't want to be a polyiana
about it, but they're they're not
supposed to do that without a warrant.
Are they doing that without a
warrant?
>> Without a warrant,
you know, at the CIA.
>> I mean, that's disturbing. My god. In
training, they used to tell us all the
time, "Our job is to break the law." And
I remember saying, "Yeah, but not here.
The job is to break the law over there."
>> You know, I was perfectly happy and and
on multiple occasions actively
participated in, you know, breaking into
people's houses or offices and planting
bugs and cameras. We're the good guys.
That's what we have to do. This is to
protect the United States. But not here.
You need a warrant. And besides, the CIA
is forbidden by law from doing anything
operationally inside the United States.
That's what the FBI is for. I just never
understood this. Like, why isn't it that
clear to everybody? I don't know.
>> Do Do you think the FBI is doing similar
behaviors or is this all CIA?
>> You know, it was my experience when I
was working with the FBI and I worked
with the FBI for years and years that
they they really were sticklers for the
law where the CIA wasn't. Um, I remember
even saying one time I I'm gonna I'm
gonna fudge the details here for obvious
reasons, but they we were talking a
couple of us CIA people were talking to
a group from the FBI and they were
saying what difficulty they were having
infiltrating a domestic terrorist group.
And I said, "Oh, no. I I I got you
covered." I said, "There was this group
that that we took care of. We we just
didn't have access to them. So, what we
did is we found one of them. It was only
like six members of this terrorist
group. We found one and we said, "Hey,
listen. Uh, Muhammad, your friend
Abdullah, I'm from the CIA, and Abdullah
told me that that you you'd be a good
guy for me to talk to because Abdullah
works for me." And and he said, "You'd
like to work for me, too." Well, the guy
runs screaming from the room, but he
goes back and he kills Abdullah.
And then we and then we tell Rashid,
"Hey, listen. We were talking about
about Abdullah with Muhammad. you know,
Muhammad's one of our guys and uh and he
told us that Abdullah was a bad guy and
then Rashad kills Muhammad. And then by
the end of the year, this terrorist
group doesn't exist anymore. And the FBI
guys said, "Oh my god, that's so
illegal. We couldn't possibly do that."
And I was like, "Oh, it never even
occurred to me that that might be
illegal." So the FBI does kind of pay
closer attention, at least they're
supposed to, to what's legal and what's
not legal. With the CIA operating
overseas, you know, who cares what's
legal and what's not legal?
>> They can do anything they want over
there. And what about domestically? I
mean, I I was a big fan of that show,
The Americans, Matthew Reese.
>> Wonderful show,
>> right? It was so good.
>> Is that real? I mean, do you think there
are a bunch of foreign spies like
sleeper spies here in America?
>> Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. That show was uh was
written and created by Joe Weisberg. Joe
was a colleague of mine in the CIA
counterterrorism center. He was a
brilliant writer. And I went to the
office one day and he walked up to me
and he said, "Hey, listen. I quit this
morning." And I was like, "What? Why
would you do that?" And he said, "This
job is just not for me. I'm not married.
I don't have any kids. I'm going to go
to Hollywood and find my fortune." And
he went to Hollywood and he created The
Americans. And the reason why it was so
successful was because it was completely
real. Just in the last two years, I
happen to live in Arlington, Virginia.
In the last two years, one of my
neighbors was arrested. She was a an
elementary school substitute teacher.
She was arrested because she was a
Russian sleeper agent
just sitting in place and waiting to be
activated by the SVR. This is something
that the Russians have always been very
good at, the long game. They'll they'll
recruit an agent, put them in place,
have them pretend to be an American, and
just let them sit there for 20 years, 30
years until they need to be activated to
carry out some operation.
>> Wow. Wow. I mean, the odds are we've all
met one and have no idea.
>> That's right.
>> That's incredible to think about that
they've been lying and wait there. The
Russians will play the long game. The
Chinese will play the long game, too.
That's one of the problems we're up
against. They're thinking
generationally. They're thinking the
next 50 years. Exactly. Right. How will
they be positioned versus how will we be
positioned? And and this is part of our
problem. Um I just want I forgive me for
diverting the discussion, but this just
breaking.
>> Uh Pam Bondi is out as we reported at
the top of the show. We had heard she
would be uh the the president just
tweeting Pam Bondi or posting on True
Social is a great American patriot and a
loyal friend who faith faithfully served
as my AG over the past year. She did a
tremendous job overseeing a massive
crackdown in crime across our country
with murders plummeting to their lowest
level since 1900. We love Pam and she
will be transitioning to a much needed
and important new job in the private
sector to be announced at a date in the
near future. Okay, I don't know what
that means. And our deputy attorney
general and a very talented and
respected legal mind, Todd Blanch, will
step in to serve as acting aging AG. Um,
so we'll see. The earlier reports were
that he w was probably going to give the
the replacement to EPA administer Lee
Zeldon. Todd Blanch makes a lot more
sense, not only because of his job
title, but because I hear he's very
well-liked over there. That's right.
>> Um, so we shall see. Pam Bondi's
officially out. Did you you have any
thoughts on that? Like why she's like
why now? Why is Pam Bondi gone now?
>> You know, I've always heard the
loveliest things about Pam Bondi that
she's a a sweetheart of a person. She's
loyal to the president. I also heard
that she never really wanted to be
attorney general. The president insisted
that she be attorney general. And you
know, when when a president calls you
and says, "Your country needs you," you
say, "Of course, Mr. President. I'll do
whatever the country needs." And I think
that's what she did. I think she really
wasn't happy in that job. And that after
a year, it was probably time to move on.
I wonder because I mean the reports are
that he was unhappy with her which is
why she she got pushed out. But I mean I
will say it's such a thankless job.
>> My information is they're all miserable
over there in DOJ for good reason. They
have way too many cases and way too few
bodies. They had a bunch of people quit
over the politics of the administration.
So that's even fewer bodies. But like a
lot of lawfare, you know, by the Trump
administration against the Trump
administration. These judges who think
they're mini president. It's just zero
free time, zero thanks, zero love, you
know, coming back from the p public. I
whatever Pam Body's going to do next,
especially if it's private sector, I
guarantee she's going to be happier.
>> So, we'll see what happens with Todd
Blanch. Okay, but back to you. Um, so
the CIA doesn't have any real rules
overseas. The FBI domestically does.
I've heard you say before another group
that has no rules is the Israelis. And
that seems really clear right now. I
mean, one of the dynamics of this war
has been the president going out there
saying, "We are talking to somebody. I
can't tell you who it is cuz I'm worried
he'll get killed." And then, of course,
left unsaid is killed by who? Obviously,
it's the Israelis.
>> So, what was your experience with them?
>> It was universally negative. Uh on in my
very first briefing, I had only been on
the job as an Iraq analyst for six
weeks. My boss said to me, "I want you
to participate in a group briefing.
You're going to brief the Israelis. They
have a Shinbet representative and a
Mossad representative." And he said, "We
don't we don't speak to the Israelis in
the building. They're not permitted in
the building." Because every time they
would come to CIA headquarters, they
would bring gifts. And the gri gifts
were always laden with listening devices
and batteries and you know we we would
x-ray everything and and we would tell
them stop trying to bug our conference
rooms and they would say oh okay okay
you caught us okay so finally we said
they just can't come in anymore so we we
have a safe house where we meet with the
Israelis so it was like eight of us the
senior Iraq analysts the military
analysts the political analysts the econ
analysts the oil analyst Everybody's
doing their thing. And because I was the
most junior, I went last. And um I said
because I was an overt employee, my name
is John Kiryaku and I'm going to brief
you today on Saddam Hussein's state of
mind. And the Mossad representative
looked over his glasses at me and he
said, "Uh, spell your name." So I
spelled it and he says to me in front of
everybody, he says, "You are Jewish."
And I said, 'I am not not recruitable.
Don't even think about trying to recruit
me. Shame on you. So I went back to the
office. My boss said, "How'd it go?" I
said, "I'm so angry right now. I could
explode." I said, he practically pitched
me right there in the meeting and asked
if I was Jewish. And he laughed and he
said, "They've done that to every single
one of us."
>> On my
>> trying to get you to turn against your
>> country for them. On my very first day
at the CIA where, you know, you put your
hand up in the air and you swear to
uphold and protect the Constitution
against all enemies, foreign and
domestic, uh, we had a briefing by the
CIA's director of security and he told
us that there are two intelligence
representatives at the Israeli embassy,
one from Mossad, one from Shinbet. He
said, "But the FBI has been able to
identify
187 other undeclared Israeli
intelligence officers spread out all
across America working to steal secrets
from American defense contractors. But
politically,
the relationship is so close that you
don't want to rock the boat and uh, you
know, start arresting people spying for
Israel. Look at Jonathan Pard. he does
every day of a 30-year sentence and then
is welcomed like some kind of a
conquering hero at the American embassy
in Jerusalem Jerusalem. It made me sick
to my stomach.
>> Well, when you said that comment about
how everybody in Congress is afraid of
the CIA, the same is true when it comes
to Israel. I don't know if afraid is the
word, but but controlled by. I mean, one
of the dynamics of this the wake of the
Iran war, John, has been
>> the not just like the loudest, but kind
of the only front-facing critics have
been from the more isolationist right.
Where are the Democrats? Where are they?
They don't say anything.
>> That's the question right there. Where
in the world are the Democrats? They are
utterly silent. In fact, I'll tell you,
I was especially furious with Cy Booker,
the Democratic senator from New Jersey.
Not the last time uh Netanyahu came to
Washington, but the time before, Cy
Booker literally ran through the halls
of Congress to get to a photo op so he
could stand behind Benjamin Netanyahu
with this big stupid grin on his face.
Like even now after Gaza, after the
start of Iran, now you're running like
OJ Simpson through an airport in in the
old I'm dating myself, but in the old uh
whatever it was commercial Yeah. Herz
commercial. You want to be in a picture
with Benjamin Netanyahu.
Some of them are afraid of being
primared and and God knows that that
Apac if you are not 100% pro-Israel in
your voting record, they will primary
you and they will spend millions of
dollars to defeat you. That scares
most uh members of Congress. And so
they're just not willing to challenge
anybody. I'll tell you another thing. I
used to be the chief investigator on the
Senate Foreign Relations Committee. I
did that from 09 to 11. And um
a couple of days after I started the
job, uh these two guys came in clearly
obviously from Apac and they said, "Hey,
welcome to Capitol Hill." I said,
"Thanks. I've worked on Capitol Hill
before. Um we want to invite you for an
all expenses paid trip to the Holy
Land." They didn't say Israel.
>> Totally.
>> And I said, "Thanks, guys. I can pay for
my own vacations. I'm not interested.
It's all expenses paid and we're going
to take you to all the Christian holy
sites. I go, "Guys,
I'm not taking Apac's money. I'm not
interested."
But I don't think a single day went by
where I didn't see those two. They were
they practically had offices up there.
And then individual House members say
that there are Apac reps that will go to
their office every day and just sit on
the couch. And if constituents come in
to meet with staff or to meet with the
member of Congress, these guys will get
up like it's their office and say,
"Remember Israel, Israel, Israel,
Israel, remember." What is that?
>> That's that's not the American way. I I
think that the manipulation is so
ubiquitous, you almost just don't even
know it's happening because everyone's
singing from the same himnil. And so
it's like, yeah, this is what we all
think. I remember at Fox News, it was
like a knee-jerk thing. You had to say
like, in Israel, we have a very special
relationship. You know, they're our most
important ally in the Middle East. And
every once in a while, I would remember
to ask why. Why again? Like, you know,
>> to have somebody explain that to me. And
it always kind of petered out after
that, like why? Again, it was also about
demonizing the Arab states. You know,
we're supposed to hate them because
they're Muslim. We're supposed to love
Israel because they're supposedly with
us in the Judeo-Christian uh you know,
narrative. I I it's there's been such a
manipulation, paid for, a paid for
manipulation that I think many of us
just starting to see. John
>> Benjamin Netanyahu said something that
was very um very much overlooked and I
think very disturbing last week. He was
giving he he had given a speech and an
Israeli reporter asked him a question
about the American Israeli war against
Iran and he corrected her and he said
it's the American war against Iran. We
are America's ally.
>> And I thought, oh buddy, that's not what
you were saying two weeks ago. Now, now
we stand alone doing your dirty work.
>> But that's what it's come down to.
>> That's clearly where it is. And he's
already saying there many reports out
from Israeli TV saying if we do go boots
on the ground, it won't be with them.
That's right.
>> They're they're boots on the ground in
Lebanon. They've got another issue
they've taken on where a million
Lebanese have been displaced because
really Israel wants to be the hgeimon of
the region and saw an opportunity here
>> and uh so we'll be on our own. It'll be
American blood and treasure that spills
on
>> Car Island. I think you're exactly
right. Israeli our
>> right our super tight allies will let us
do their bidding. I mean, it's just I
believe every word of what you said
about how they've tried to get every
president to do this and unfortunately
Trump was the taker. Trump was the one
who was talked into it as he watched too
much Fox News
>> and he got persuaded by the messaging
that's there. Okay, but back to you.
Back to you.
>> One of the things I heard you say about
yourself is that
>> you have sociopathic tendencies. Now,
what does that mean?
>> The CIA actively seeks to hire people
who have sociopathic tendencies, not
sociopaths. Sociopaths have no
conscience. They don't feel guilt or
remorse. They blow right through the
polygraph because they don't react to
anything. People who have sociopathic
tendencies do have a conscience. They do
feel guilt or remorse, but they're
willing to break the law or to work in
legal, moral, and ethical gray areas if
they believe it's the right thing to do.
So, I mentioned earlier that on multiple
occasions I broke into people's houses
or businesses and and planted
microphones or listening devices. I was
very happy to do that because I believed
we were the good guys and this was to
protect America, right? We've got to
disrupt that next attack. We need to
take apart this terrorist group. And if
that means, you know, identifying a
terrorist apartment and renting the
apartment underneath and drilling a hole
through the floor so I can stick a
pinhole camera and listen or a
microphone and listen to everything
that's being said and then report it
back to CIA headquarters. I'm going to
do it. That's what a sociopathic
tendency is
>> to you. Are you able to go anywhere now
or rent an apartment? Like I mean, are
you constantly wondering whether this
this is being done to you?
>> Oh, yeah.
Oh, I I just assume that it is. Sure.
And you know, that's why
one of the reasons why I'm so vocal and
so public is I figured it's safer for me
because more people would miss me if
something were to happen. Y
>> I will add I will add that an investment
in a good bulletproof vest is always
wise as well.
>> And um
>> Oh my gosh, what do you have that just
sitting in your house? What's that doing
right next to you? I gave a speech the
other day and it was so uncomfortable I
took it off when I got when I got home.
Um, but you know, after Charlie Kirk and
after these revelations from Wikileaks
about what the CIA does and what the FBI
does and what the Israelis do, they kill
everybody who they don't like. So, you
know, better safe than sorry.
>> I mean, let me ask you like without
getting too graphic, but like
let's say you're, you know, you're being
intimate in your home, you're in an
intimate position. Like do you do you
remove all phones? Do you make sure
there's no TVs in the room? Like is it
at that level where it's like
everything's exposed?
>> Yeah, it it's at that level. Yes. I hate
to say it. You know, all I have is like
a little one of those waterproof shower
radios so I can at least listen to the
news in the morning. But yeah, that's
that's pretty much it.
>> Are you not into smart technology for
this reason? You know, forgive me
because I'm going to sound like a
hypocrite, but I do have I'm not going
to say the name because it's going to
light up an alexa in my kitchen because
I sometimes ask for recipes or the
weather and I don't say anything in the
kitchen. You know, what who am I going
to talk to myself? So, yeah, but that's
that's the only that's the only smart
technology that I allow myself.
I mean, I my own thought has been I you
just kind of have to be a relatively
good person or just accept that your
foibless are no more bizarre than
anybody else's because they probably do
know everything. I mean, that's
>> I I'm going to blow my own whistle or
blow Yeah. blow my own horn here. Uh
when the FBI raided my house, when John
Brennan
took out this vendetta against me, um
they confiscated all of my electronics
and they gave it all back to me a year
later. And one of the FBI agents said,
"You know, this was the first time in my
career that we ever that we ever uh took
somebody's electronics and we didn't
find any porn." And I said, "What do you
think? I'm an animal."
>> Oh, no way.
>> Yeah.
No way. Well, you know, my
understanding, too, is that the Israelis
own a couple of the big porn sites that
we the one guy just died. He owned Only
Fans. I don't we can't remember if he
was an an American or as an Israeli, but
either way, he was very sympathetic
towards Israel.
>> But that's another way because if they
can turn that camera around at you, I
mean, there you're done.
>> That that'd be a great way to blackmail
somebody. It
>> sure would be. Yeah. They they've been
the kings of the porn industry for
decades. Whether it's in Brooklyn, it's
heavily uh based in Brooklyn, or in uh
oh, what's it called? Hawthorne,
California, up by Northridge. Yeah.
That's the the two bases of the porn
industry, and it's almost exclusively
Israeli.
>> Wow. Yeah. The guy who owned Only Fans
was Ukrainian American, but a big a big
fan of Israel. Uh and donated a lot of
money. It's it's all like I have I've
said many times, in today's day and age,
it's not enough to pretend. You actually
have to be a good person now. It's going
to be a massive pain in the ass. Oh my
god. Yes. But we're going to have to
just grin and bear it. Try to be better
people. John, I I really hope to
continue this conversation. I want to
hear so much more about you and your
opinions. Loved, love, loved meeting.
>> The pleasure is all mine. Thanks again
for the invitation. It was very kind.
>> Oh, to be continued. All the best. Wow.
What a fascinating guy. I mean, what a
life, right? that like to be in the
intel agencies to be recruited by your
college graduate school professor and
then wind up in prison. We didn't even
get to the prison stuff but lots to go
over. Okay, tomorrow we are back with
Moren Callahan for the full show. We
will see you then.